Cohen, Abraham "Coordinated Bargaining at General Electric: An Analysis" Dissertation Supporting Documentation /3017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Abraham Cohen "Coordinated Bargaining at General Electric: An Analysis" Dissertation Supporting Documentation
1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cohen, Abraham
/3017
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Correspondence, papers (documents), publications (documents).
Annual reports, statements from the UAW, news releases, news bulletins, agreement proposals, flyers and correspondence.
3071993
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 20, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 15, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining -- Electric industries -- United States -- Case studies; Cohen, Abraham, 1932-
3071993
- GE Annual Report, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- GE Annual Reports, 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- CBC Issues and Answers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Summary of GM Proposal to UAW, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  September 1, 1970.
- Statements from UAW [folder 1 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Retirement Security, Insurance and Sub-Administration, Cost of Living Allowance, Wage Equity
- Statements from UAW [folder 2 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Inverse Security, Apprentice Section, Area Hire, Back Pay, Benefit Plans
- Statements from UAW [folder 3 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Discipline, Use of Time Clocks, Garnishments, Group Life Insurance, Harmony Clause
- Statements from UAW [folder 4 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Health/Safety Control, Health Program, Holidays, Plant Employment, Vacations
- Statements from UAW [folder 5 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Miscellaneous Payments, Blood Donor, New Jobs, Non-Discrimination, Optional Overtime, Orientation
- Statements from UAW [folder 6 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Production Standards, Alcoholism, Promotions and Transfers, Relief, Representation
- Statements from UAW [folder 7 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Seniority, Skilled Trades, Stock Purchase Plan, Students (etc.), Subcontracting
- Statements from UAW [folder 8 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Supervisory Employees, Sub-Plan, Training/Education, Tuition, Wages, Working Hours
- GM Pamphlets and Articles (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Statement of GM to UAW, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  July 21, 1970.
- GM News Releases (Box 1, Folder 15)
- GM Proposal for Three Year National Agreement with UAW (Box 1, Folder 16)
- UAW Research Department (Box 1, Folder 17)
- GM and UAW Letters (General) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- GE Corporate Employee Relations (Box 1, Folder 19)
- GE Flyers (Box 1, Folder 20)
- "Negotiation News" Bulletin [folder 1 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 21)
- "Negotiation News" Bulletin [folder 2 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 22)
- "Negotiation News" Bulletin [folder 3 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 23)
- "Negotiation News" Bulletin [folder 4 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Coordinated Bargaining (ALF-CIO-CLC) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- IUE-GE Documents (Box 1, Folder 26)
- "Program for Progress" (Box 1, Folder 27)
- "Unity" and Coordinated Bargaining Flyers (Box 1, Folder 28)
- "The Hundred Days" and "What is 'Boulwareism'?" (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Pension and Insurance Proposals Presented to GE (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Proposals to the GE Company by IUE (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Documents (Box 1, Folder 32)